國會讓美國失望
We're almost a month into the strike,
罷工已近一個月
數百萬的孩子  困在家裏無法上課
and we've got millions of kids  stuck home from school.
你怪罪白宮或國會嗎？
Do you blame the White House or Congress?
我個人不同情教師
I personally have very little sympathy  for the teachers.
國會讓教師失望
We're over three weeks into this strike.
罷工已三周
耗損全國數十億美元
It's costing the country billions of dollars,
- 未找出解決之道…  - 表明立場
-and instead of offering solutions...  -There's a big difference between
和坐視不理差很多
taking a stand and sitting on your hands.
工會流乾稅賦！
不知道要叫懦弱…
I don't know whether to call it cowardice...
這是他的議程
It's his agenda.
教師應教書…  回家
問題是他剽竊合理的傳統理想
And the problem is that he stole  sound, conservative ideas.
他做的明智之舉  就是抄襲共和黨政綱
The only smart thing he's done is lift  his platform from the Republican platform.
我承認，琳達  這出乎我意料之外
I admit it, Linda. This got away from me.
但是我們無法讓時光倒流  我們得堅持立場
But we can't turn back time.  We have to hold our ground.
不管我們的支持率繼續下滑？
While our approval ratings  continue to nosedive?
多年來史皮奈拉和我合作  數十件勞工提案
Spinella and I worked together for years  on dozens of labor-related bills.
- 我以為他會很理性  - 你錯了
-I thought he'd be reasonable.  -Well, you were wrong about that.
沒料到他會瘋到展開罷工
Well, I didn't think he'd be  insane enough to go on strike,
也沒料到罷工會持續這麼久
and I didn't think the strike  would last this long.
你錯估這事件兩次
So you've been wrong twice about this.
我怎能相信堅持立場是對的？
Why should I believe  you're right about holding out?
我們威脅勞資談判是為了
We threatened collective  bargaining in order to get
成績標準和特許補助
performance standards and charter funding.
那是我們談好的立場
That's the deal that we made.  We took that stand.
現在若讓步，就全盤皆輸
We lay down now, we lose it all.
沒有改革，只有空洞的提案
There'll be no reform, just an empty bill.
我瞭解這個邏輯，法蘭  但現在得做損害控制
I understand the logic, Frank,  but we're in damage control now.
但是我們無法止這個血  卻弄出另一個傷口
But we can't close one wound  by opening another.
我們是民主黨
But we're the Democrats.
我們該為教師喉舌
We're the ones who are supposed  to be defending the teachers.
魚與熊掌無法兼得，琳達
But you can't have it both ways, Linda.
無法達到改革
You can't have the reform you want
又滿足教師
and keep the teachers happy  at the same time.
從一開始你就知道
You knew that when we started.
好吧，若讓我們選擇  我們該滿足教師
Okay, then if we have to choose,  we choose to keep the teachers happy.
那就大錯特錯，琳達  我們已無法回頭
That is a mistake, Linda.  We've already crossed the Rubicon.
我跟你說，總統希望改變提案
I'm telling you this.  The President wants to change the bill.
三周前就該這麼做
We should've done it three weeks ago.
我們當時沒做  所以現在你得照做
We didn't. So you have to do it now.
琳達，請再給我多點時間
Give me more time, Linda, please.
如果我能停止罷工  保留我們要的提案內容
If I can break this strike and get  everything we want in this bill,
這不是比讓步更好嗎？
can we agree that's preferable to folding?
如果能辦到…
Of course. If we can count on that...
那就相信我，再給我一周
Then count on me for just one more week.
若到時罷工還沒停止  我就修改提案
If the strike isn't over by then,  I'll change the bill.
- 法蘭…  - 再一周就好
-Frank...  -No. One more week. That's all.
真是再糟也不過了
This is the worst possible position to be in.
如果我修改提案  總統還是會覺得我失敗
If I water down the bill,  the President will still see me as a failure.
如果罷工一周內沒結束  我就窮途末路
If the strike doesn't end in a week,  I've forced myself into a corner.
只有全面勝利  才能讓我重獲他的青睞
Only total victory will put me  back in his good graces.
否則就是出局
The alternative is exile,
之前五個月就是白忙一場
which would mean  the last five months were for nothing.
我不能跌回原點
I cannot abide falling back to square one.
夫人，議員找我嗎？
Does the Congressman need me, ma'am?
不，我只是想邀你喝杯咖啡
No. I just was wondering  if you wanted a cup of coffee.
我剛煮了一壺
I just brewed a fresh pot.
- 夫人，不用了，謝謝  - 確定？
-I'm good, ma'am. But thanks.  -Are you sure?
我再幾個小時就下班了，沒事
My shift's done in a couple hours. I'll be fine.
來吧，放鬆一下
You know, come on. Stretch your legs.
我可不接受拒絕
I won't take no for an answer.
你當議員保鑣前做什麼工作？
What did you do before you  joined the leadership detail?
我在華府當警察
I was a cop here in D.C.
在那之前  我在海軍陸戰隊服役，夫人
Before that, I was in the Marines, ma'am.
- 謝謝  - 你有在國外服役嗎？
-Thank you.  -Did you serve overseas?
有的，夫人，巴林  之後去阿富汗
I did, ma'am. Bahrain, then Afghanistan.
第二次派駐海外  主要是在可蘭山谷
Served most of my second tour  in the Korengal Valley.
你想知道我是否殺過人？
You wanna know if I killed anyone?
我想我知道答案
I think I know the answer.
我約了柏許晚餐，我要…
I got a dinner meeting with Birch. I'll be...
我邀他來喝咖啡
I invited him in for coffee.
喝快點，要出發了…
Well, drink it fast. We leave in five...
趴下！遠離窗戶！
Get down! Stay away from the windows!
停下！
Stop!
我會安排六名優秀手下  24小時保護你們
You'll have six of my best men  covering you around the clock.
那你之前為什麼沒安排
I guess I'm wondering why  we didn't at least have
其中一個優秀手下保護我們
one of your best men covering us now.
他會被懲戒的，議員
He'll be disciplined, sir.
他在住宅區開槍
He shot a gun in a residential neighborhood.
- 開除他  - 我們會仔細調查
-I want him fired.  -There will be a full investigation,
採取必要措施
and we'll take the necessary action.
史提夫絕不會讓這種事發生
Steve never would've let this happen.
他好點了嗎？  有他在，我會覺得安全多了
Is he better yet? Because I would  feel a lot safer if he was with us.
遺憾的是  他不會再回來了，議員
Unfortunately, he won't be coming back, sir.
我以為他只是膽囊感染
I thought he just had a gallbladder infection.
沒錯，但不只這些
He did, they found more.
他得了胰腺癌末期
His pancreas, stage four.
- 老天  - 天啊，這麼嚴重
-Jesus.  -Oh, my God. That's awful.
他還能活多久？
How much longer does he have?
不長，幾周
Not long. A few weeks.
至少他老婆是這麼告訴我的
At least that's what his wife told me.
我們必須去看他  你能查出他在哪嗎？
We have to go see him.  Can you get the information where he is?
當然，我會馬上告知
Of course.  I'll make sure you get it right away.
- 謝謝，隊長  - 謝謝
-Thank you, Captain.  -Thank you.
不客氣，晚安
You're welcome. Good night.
- 前門  - 是的，長官
-Front door.  -Yes, sir.
你的佩槍
Your weapon.
還有你的徽章
Your badge, too.
長官，要我停職？
Am I suspended, sir?
嫌犯徒步逃跑  你居然對他開槍？
You had a suspect on foot,  and you fire your gun?
- 長官，我知道…  - 知道我多有丟人嗎？
-Sir, I realize that...  -Do you know how this reflects on me?
我的手下居然如此魯莽？
That one of our men could be so careless?
你不只擅離職守去喝咖啡
Not only do you abandon  your post for coffee.
還有可能射傷路人
You could've killed a bystander.
那顆子彈是在某家前廊找到的
That slug was found  on somebody's front stoop.
要是射進他們家呢？
What if it went in their house?
你的徽章，米契
Your badge, Meechum.
兩個原因，其實都一樣
Two reasons,  which are really the same reason.
我受夠了為別人工作
I was sick of working for other people,
我知道我比我的老闆還能幹
and I knew I could do a better job  than my bosses.
他們不斷壓迫、排斥我
They kept trying to suppress me,  shutting me out.
於是我說：  「我自己來」
So I said, "Fuck it. I'll do it my way."
- 然後你就辭職了？  - 和你不一樣
-And then you just quit?  -Not like you did.
我拚死拚活工作  才存夠錢開《頭條報導》
I slaved away until I lined up  the money to start Slugline.
《頭條報導》茁壯之後  你打算如何？
Once Slugline gets big enough,  what's the plan?
像亞莉安娜一樣賣了公司？
Are you gonna sell it like Arianna?
可能吧，之後誰知道？
Probably. And then who knows?
迎接任何挑戰，或許去上海吧
Whatever the next adventure is.  Maybe Shanghai.
所以我可能沒辦法做兩年？
So I shouldn't expect  to have a job in two years?
你會想兩年  都做同一份工作嗎？
Do you ever wanna have any job  for more than two years?
你呢？你有什麼雄心壯志？
What about you? What's your big plan?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
拜託，  《頭條報導》  只是你的踏腳板
Come on.  Slugline is just a stepping stone for you.
- 我得接個電話  - 去忙吧
-You know what? I should take this.  -Go. Do your thing.
你有證據  證明是史皮奈拉做的嗎？
Hey. Do you have proof  Spinella was behind it?
寫下來  全國教師罷工第三周後…
Put it in context.  Three weeks into a national teachers' strike...
提案負責人  法蘭斯安德沃的私宅…
At the home of Francis Underwood,  who has led the charge on...
就是這樣，趕快發文  免得我鄰居通知地方晚間新聞
There you go. Now post that before one of  my neighbors calls a local 11:00 hack.
- 我何時再見你？  - 我是受害人
-When do I see you next?  -I'm background on this.
- 不是你的線人  - 現在不方便？
-I'm not your source.  -You can't talk now?
- 對  - 何時？
-No.  -When?
很快，迫不及待
Soon, with bells on.
「多些書，少些磚塊」如何？
What about  "more school books, less bricks"?
太廣泛了  我們要更一針見血
No, it's too broad.  We need a better sound bite.
更精準、更能將矛頭  指向史皮奈拉的話
Something specific, something that  points the finger directly at Spinella.
- 他會否認涉案  - 當然了
-He'll deny any involvement.  -Well, of course he will.
- 要怎麼辦？  - 就說他管不好手下的人
-So how do we get around that?  -We say he can't control his troops.
- 沒有證據是教師做的  - 還會是誰？
-There's no evidence it was a teacher.  -Who else could it be?
他會將罷工怪在國會頭上
Look, he's gonna shift blame for  the strike back on Congress.
我們要更明確、清新的標語
No. We need something clear,  something clean,
聽了就忘不了的
something that sticks in your head.
「教師得學會自製」
"Teachers need a lesson in self-restraint."
你沒聽懂我的意思  大家都愛戴教師
No. You're not hearing me.  People like teachers.
我們要能讓史皮奈拉  變成壞人的標語
No. We need something  that makes Spinella the villain.
- 他無控制力，無法…  - 失序勞工
-His lack of control, his inability...  -Disorganized labor.
失序勞工，直接簡單
It's disorganized labor, plain and simple.
教師罷工轉向暴力
憤怒的教師  朝議員住宅窗戶扔磚塊
When you've got angry teachers throwing  bricks through congressmen's windows,
那是工會領袖的責任
you've gotta blame the union leadership.
我們會為高階議員增加保安
We'll be beefing up the security  for the entire leadership.
我強烈建議馬帝史皮奈拉  管好他的人
And I strongly encourage Marty Spinella  to keep his people in line.
這變得像是失序勞工了
This is starting to look like  disorganized labor.
你真的認為  是馬帝史皮奈拉的錯？
Do you really think  Marty Spinella is to blame?
不論史皮奈拉先生  是否是幕後主使
Whether Mr. Spinella is behind this or not,
他都該注意言詞
he might wanna tone down the rhetoric,
以免失序勞工變成組織犯罪
before disorganized labor  turns into organized crime.
沒人能證明這點  這就是最有力的回應
No one can prove anything.  So that's the most cogent response.
那就上電視說明  你譴責一切形式的暴力
Well, go on TV and say that.  You deplore violence in any form.
該負責任的是國會
It's Congress that should take responsibility.
我不想自貶到法蘭的水平
I don't want to degenerate to Frank's level.
我們得結束磚塊事件  這分散大家對議題的注意力
We need to kill this brick thing.  It's distracting people from the issues.
- 說得對  - 熱度過了，就會消失
-She's right.  -lt'll eat up one cycle, and it'll disappear.
不，這個故事越來越引人關注
No. This story is getting traction.
- 罷工支持率在下降  - 總統支持率也是
-Support for the strike is dipping.  -So is the President's approval ratings.
但不管如何，他還能執政三年
But he gets to stay in the Oval Office  another three years, no matter what.
再拖三周我們可承受不了
We can't afford another three weeks.
我叫工會罷工時  就說過要準備好長期抗戰
When I told the unions to strike,  I told them to prepare for the long haul.
就算他們沒錢了  我們還是繼續罷工
All right? Their accounts dry up,  we keep going.
我們會想出方法  我絕不會對這種事讓步
We figure it out. I am not going  to blink over something like this.
好，但要是輸了這場公關戰
Fine. But ifwe lose  the public relations battle,
堅持可毫無好處
none of that does us any good.
法蘭要我們採取防守
Frank wants us on the defensive.
這件事會平息的
I think this story is going to blow over.
如果我錯了，我們會重新評估
If I'm wrong, we'll reevaluate.
但是我想再堅持一、兩天  好嗎？
But I wanna give it  another day or two first. Okay?
亞當
Hi, Adam.
你還好嗎？我看到新聞了
You all right? I saw the news.
我沒事
Yes, I'm fine.
一定把你嚇壞了
That's gotta rattle the nerves.
磚頭居然破窗而入
Brick coming through the window.
的確有點
It did, some.
你還住在家裏嗎？
So are you staying in the house?
現在有加派保安人員，所以…
We've got extra security now, so...
我擔心你，所以想問候你
Well, it made me think of you,  so I figured I'd just check in.
真是謝謝
I appreciate that.
我們還沒談呢？
We still haven't talked, have we?
- 沒必要  - 我覺得有必要
-There's no need to.  -I think we should.
我是這麼想的
Here's how I see it.
你要我過去，我去了
You asked me to come down. I did.
我們都理解那代表的意義
We both had ideas  about what that could mean.
或許相差無幾
Probably very similar ideas.
但之後你改變主意
But then you changed your mind.
那就這樣吧
So be it.
我們還是可以連絡  或繼續當朋友
There's no reason we can't be in touch  or remain friends.
別自欺欺人了，亞當
Let's not fool ourselves, Adam.
我不會再打電話給你
So I won't call again.
- 結束了  - 這不是我的意思
-Done.  -I'm not saying that.
那你的意思是？
What are you saying?
我只是關心你才打電話
I just called because I care about you.
沒別的意思
No agenda.
如果你想再談，就打電話給我
If you wanna talk again, call me.
若不想，我瞭解，隨你決定
If not, I understand. It's up to you.
你覺得我無理取鬧？
You think I'm being unreasonable?
我覺得你是做你該做的事
I think you're doing  whatever it is you need to do,
我不會質疑這點
and I'm not gonna question it.
你打電話來真好
It was sweet of you to call.
你大概得繼續工作了
Listen, you probably  need to get back to work.
我得繼續工作，該掛電話了
I know I do. I should go.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
- 保重  - 好
-Take care.  -Okay.
- 法蘭，有時間嗎？  - 裏面見
-Frank, you got a minute?  -I'll see you inside.
我想當州長，希望你能幫忙
I wanna be governor, and I want your help.
- 我還在人選名單上嗎？  - 是的
-Am I still on the short list?  -You are.
我一個多月滴酒不沾  我戒酒了
I haven't had a drink  in over a month. I'm clean.
這是因為我要求你戒酒  還是你想戒酒？
Is that because I asked,  or because it's what you want?
該是我對自己負責的時候
It was about time I took  responsibility for myself.
負責是一回事，值得欽佩
Taking responsibility is one thing,  and it's admirable.
但是競選大州的州長  就另當別論了
But running for governor of a major  state is a whole nother ball game.
法蘭，我跟你說，我入選國會
Let me tell you something, Frank.  I got elected to Congress
那是因為我抓住機會
'cause I seized the moment  that opportunity struck.
你把我留在名單上  我想抓住那機會
You kept me on that list.  I wanna seize that opportunity.
如果你幫我的忙  我會為你付出一切
If you help me out,  I'll give you everything I got.
我就在等你這句話
Well, that's all I've been waiting to hear.
好吧，我跟你說
All right. I'll tell you what.
我得打幾通電話  和一些人談談
I need to make some calls,  check in with some people.
給我幾天，我再回覆
Give me a few days. I'll get back to you.
- 當然  - 還有，彼得…
-Of course.  -And, Peter...
我總算看到真正的你
I feel like I've met the real you  for the first time just now.
珍妮
Janet.
- 不方便嗎？  - 不會
-ls this a bad time?  -No.
一點也不會
No, not at all.
抱歉，我不知道你會來
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were coming.
坐我的椅子吧
Here. Take my chair.
- 不用，沒事  - 我來拿花
-No. I'm fine.  -I'll take these.
謝謝
Thank you.
- 你好，史提夫  - 你好
-Hello, Steve.  -Hey.
花需要加點水，我馬上回來
These could use some water.  I'll be right back.
法蘭斯和我知道時很難過
Francis and I were so upset when we heard.
抱歉我沒能早點來
I'm sorry I haven't come sooner.
我不想要太多人知道
I didn't want too many people knowing.
我明白
Yes.
法蘭斯很想過來
Francis wishes he could be here.
他希望你知道他為你禱告
He wants you to know he's praying for you.
來不成？
Couldn't make it?
沒辦法  現在有大規模的教師罷工
No, there's a big teachers' strike  going on right now,
他困在辦公室好幾周了
and he's been stuck in his office for weeks.
我懂，我有看到新聞
I get it. I saw the news.
- 磚頭  - 對
-The brick.  -Right.
我跟法蘭斯說  若你在場，可能就不會發生了
I told Francis that probably wouldn't  have happened if you were there.
可能不會
No. Probably not.
我從未見過他禱告
I never seen him pray.
這八年都沒見過
Not in eight years.
你說他為我禱告
You said he was praying for me.
你看過我們上教堂
You've seen us in church.
對，但是我從未進到教堂裏面
Yeah, but I never went inside.
這些花真美
They're just gorgeous.
安德沃夫人，謝謝你
Mrs. Underwood, thank you so much.
叫我克萊兒就好
Please, call me Claire.
- 我知道你還有事要忙  - 是的
-I know you got things to do.  -Of course.
若你有什麼需要，就連絡我  你有我的手機號碼
If you need anything at all, call me.  You have my cell.
任何事都沒問題  很抱歉這次貿然而來
Anything at all.  And I'm sorry to have surprised you.
不會，你能來真好
No. It was so nice of you to come.
謝謝，我知道史提夫很高興
Thank you. I know Steve appreciated it.
看看這個
Check this out.
這是泡綿
It's foam.
- 這玩意我們有多少？  - 兩百個，但我能弄到更多
-How many of these we have?  -200. But I can get more.
再弄些來
Get more.
來啊！
Bring it on!
你得給教師該有的尊重
You need to give the teachers  the respect they deserve.
不能讓步了，馬帝
We can't back away from this, Marty.
- 我們得正面迎敵  - 是他們挑釁我們的
-We've gotta face it head-on.  -They provoked us.
他們丟泡綿  我們的人動的是拳腳
They were throwing foam.  Our guys were throwing punches.
我們會看起來像壞人
We're gonna come off the bad guys here.
好吧，我懂
Okay. Okay. I get it. I get it.
但我要好好解決這件事
But I wanna be smart about this.
我要一勞永逸
I wanna do something definitive  that'll put this to bed
- 讓大家回到重點
- CNN  -and get us back on message.  -CNN.
一對一，你和安德沃
One-on-one, you and Underwood.
今晚8點
8:00 tonight.
法蘭擅長辯論
Frank is excellent in debates.
強勢點  直接和他對質丟磚事件
Go strong against him.  Address the brick right to his face.
- 就這樣  - 安德沃說你去，他就去
-End of story.  -Underwood says he's in if you are.
好吧，但我要做好萬全準備
Okay. But I want as much prep  as possible, okay?
我想模擬一遍提問
I want to run questions.
你當中間人，你當安德沃
You moderate, you play Underwood.
戴這條吧
Wear this one.
再到這來，我幫你上粉
Then come in here.  I wanna put powder on you.
攝影棚的人會弄的
Well, there's somebody at the studio  can do that.
他們總是撲太多粉，我來吧
Yes, and they always cake on too much.  I'm doing it.
戰爭妝
War paint.
你覺得會多激烈？
How bloody do you think it'll be?
我會輕易擊敗他
I think I oughta be able to  dispatch with him easily enough.
你還記得彼得魯索嗎？
You remember Peter Russo?
他很好，一個月沒喝酒了
He's doing well.  He hasn't had a drink in a month.
真好，我喜歡他
Good for him. I like him.
很好，他可能需要你幫忙
Good, because he could use your help.
- 怎麼幫？  - 我們要幫他選州長
-How?  -We're running him for governor.
真有野心
Ambitious.
我們要在他的選區  創造工作機會
We wanna create jobs in his district.
在德拉瓦河
It's on the Delaware River.
我在想或許  我們能一起弄個提案
I thought we might be able  to put a bill together.
有經濟助益的提案
Something with an economic upside.
這和造船廠關閉有關？
This has to do with the shipyard closing?
我們需要造船廠員工  支持他競選
We need the shipbuilders'  support for his campaign.
你能幫他草擬  他能贊助的提案嗎？
You thinkyou might be able to draft a bill  that he can sponsor?
我想專注在國際計劃，法蘭斯
I'm really trying to focus on  international projects, Francis.
不是國內立法
Not domestic legislation.
我知道，但我真的  很需要你的幫忙，克萊兒
I understand, but I could really  use your help, Claire.
凱薩琳杜倫還欠我們人情？
Does Catherine Durant still owe us?
當你把人拱上國務卿  他們就欠你一輩子
When you make someone Secretary of State,  they owe you for life.
我們的濾水器卡在蘇丹海關
We're having trouble getting our water filters  through Sudanese customs.
- 我上車會打電話  - 明天就行了
-I'll call from the car.  -Tomorrow's fine.
- 反正都得打電話  - 我知道
-I would have done that anyway.  -I know.
我準備好開戰了
I'm ready for battle.
你要來看嗎？
You wanna come watch?
- 不了，你去吧  - 來吧
-No. You go on ahead.  -Come on.
看我怎麼打敗史皮奈拉
Watch me put the final nail  in Spinella's coffin.
會很好玩的
It'll be fun.
馬帝
Marty.
法蘭
Frank.
各位，就定位
Come on, people. Take your marks.
議員，你要回應嗎？
Congressman, would you  like to respond to that?
好的
Yes, I would.
浪費納稅人20億的辛苦錢
$2 billion of taxpayers' money  being wasted.
全國教師罷工
國會應當感到羞愧，法蘭
And Congress should be ashamed  of itself for that, Frank.
什麼？馬帝  國會有逼迫教師罷工嗎？
What? Did Congress force  the teachers to go on strike, Marty?
- 才沒有  - 法蘭，是嗎？
-No, we didn't.  -Really, Frank?
當你威脅教師工會的  協商能力
When you threaten teachers' ability  to negotiate as a union,
威脅教師的工作保障
when you threaten their job security,
威脅教師的生計
you threaten their livelihood,
你當然逼迫教師罷工
of course you force them to strike.
我們還逼迫教師  拿磚頭砸別人的房子嗎？
And did we also force them to start  throwing bricks at people's houses?
我很高興你提到這件事
You know what,  I'm really glad you brought that up,
你知道沒有證據證明
because you know  there's absolutely no proof that
這個事件和這場罷工有關
that incident had anything to do  with this strike.
我想藉此機會向大家說明
And I wanna take the opportunity  to say publicly
我們絕對譴責
that we categorically condemn
使用暴力或脅迫
any use of violence whatsoever,  or intimidation.
所以你是說
What you're saying, essentially,
你控制不好你的人
is that you can't control your own people.
- 我不是這個意思  - 你就是
-That's not what I'm saying.  -That is what you're saying.
你們毫無秩序
You're disorganized.
失序勞工
Disorganized labor.
你愛怎麼說就怎麼說
You know what, you could keep  trotting out that phrase all you like,
法蘭，但你知道我想說什麼？  我希望回歸到
but you know what I'd like to do, Frank?  I would like to get back
教育孩童的議題
to the issue here of educating our children
國會並未兌現承諾
and the fact that Congress is not  living up to their commitment.
你知道我想要什麼？
Well, you know what I would like?
什麼？
What?
道歉
An apology.
不是向我道歉  而是向我老婆道歉
If not to me, then to my wife.
磚塊砸進我家窗戶非常恐怖
When that brick came through  our window, it was terrifying.
她就站在那兒
She's standing right over there.
- 克萊兒？  - 二號鏡拍夫人
-Claire?  -We need camera two on the wife.
你何不看著她的眼睛
Now, why don't you look her in the eye
對她說  你的手下和砸磚事件無關
and tell her that your people had  nothing to do with that brick.
- 你當真？  - 對
-Are you serious?  -Yes.
好吧
Okay.
安德沃夫人，克萊兒
Mrs. Underwood, Claire,
我非常遺憾
I am sincerely sorry
你所經歷的驚嚇
that you had to go through that ordeal, truly.
這件事讓我憎惡
And it actually sickens me
居然有人讓你在自己家裏  感到不安
that someone made you  feel unsafe in your own home.
我向你擔保，據我所知
And I give you my word that  to the best of my knowledge,
我的手下和這件事無關
none of our people  had anything to do with it.
但是你知道  什麼事讓我更憎惡嗎？
But you know what sickens me more?
就是現在  你的老公居然利用你
That right now, your husband is using you
想在全國電視台贏得辯論
as a prop on national television  to try and win a debate.
所以我覺得你才是  該向你老婆道歉的人，法蘭
So I think you're the one  that owes your wife an apology, Frank.
道完歉後
And when you're done apologizing,
我們是否可以回到議題
can we please get back to the issue here
討論孩童的教育？
of educating our children?
你錯了，馬帝
No. You've got this wrong, Marty.
教育不分你我
There is no "you" and "l" in education.
當然，是有這些字母
Well, I mean, yes, there's the letters,
教育這個字有「U」和「I」
"U" and "l" are in the word education.
但是有著大寫「E」的教育…
But education with a capital "E"...
你懂我在說什麼
You know what I'm talking about.
我不懂
I don't think I do.
你懂的，馬帝
Yes, you do, Marty.
「U」和「I」、教育
"U" and "I", education.
我們要浪費  剩下的辯論時間在發母音…
So, we're gonna waste the rest of  this debate naming all the vowels in...
我很樂意玩母音遊戲
I'm happy to play the vowel game.
要和我玩嗎？
You wanna play the vowel game with me?
好吧，  「你」覺得「我」
All right. "U" think "I"
「欠」  「你」
"O" "U"
「一個」道歉？
"A" apology?
但不對
But no, no, no.
「你」  「欠」  「我」
"U" "O" "l."
真有趣  你忘了「教育」裏的「E」
Interesting. You left out "E" for "Education."
- 所以…  - 澄清
-So let...  -Defecation.
教導，抱歉
Edification. I'm sorry.
哈哈
LOL.
你這麼喜歡《芝麻街》？
You like Sesame Street so much?
何不給孩童應得的補助？
Why don't you give the kids  the money they deserve?
我想說教育是…
What I'm trying to say about education...
看來學校還沒停課
Well, I guess school's still in session.
你給我上了一課，馬帝
I guess you schooled me there, Marty.
- 我們繼續吧  - 請
-Let's move on.  -Please.
撇開幽默  這裏有更重要的議題
Humor aside, there are more  important issues out there.
我無意把你捲入這事
I had no intention of bringing you into this.
這不是我的計劃  如果是，我早就跟你說了
It wasn't part of a plan.  I would've told you if it was.
我知道
I know.
我突然想到，就脫口而出
The idea just struck me, and I went with it.
我不在乎你即興發揮
I don't mind that you improvised.
只是希望你能做得更好
I just wish you'd done it better.
在本台昨晚的辯論中  議員法蘭安德沃聲稱
Congressman Frank Underwood  says he got, quote, schooled
美國教師聯盟發言人  和首席戰略家
by AFT spokesman  and chief strategist, Martin Spinella,
馬帝史皮奈拉給他上了一課
during a debate last night on this network.
過去24小時，電視台與網路
In the past 24 hours, reruns of the gaffe
不斷重播失態片段
have played nonstop  on TV news programs and the Internet.
線上影音網站  配上合成電子音樂
A YouTube clip set to techno music
吸引30多萬人點擊
has logged more than 300, 000 hits
還衍生許多其他的諷刺內容
and spawned dozens of other spoofs.
不對
No, no, no
「你」  「欠」  「我」
"E" "O" "I"
有著大寫「E」
With a capital "E"
教育，哈哈
Education LOL
這和李哈維奧斯沃德的轉獄  一樣拙劣
That was as clumsy as the  Lee Harvey Oswald prison transfer.
他在想什麼？
What was he thinking?
稍等
Just give me one second.
這條街往下走有間小吃店
There's a deli down the street.
派翠，謝謝你來
Patti, thanks for coming.
請坐，來點咖啡？
Sit down. You want some coffee?
謝謝，我不用
No, thanks. I'm good.
昨晚有看《馬赫脫口秀》嗎？
Hey, did you see Bill Maher last night?
沒有
No, I didn't.
在討論CNN的事
It was about the CNN thing.
法蘭，我得說，真的有點好笑
I have to admit, Frank, it was kind of funny.
那我得看看重播
Well, I'll have to catch a rerun.
你還好嗎？  罷工的事還好嗎？
How you doing?  You holding up all right with the strike?
我們來談賓州吧
Let's talk about Pennsylvania.
我找到候選人了
I have your candidate.
彼得魯索，第一國會選區
Peter Russo. 1st Congressional District.
我們刪掉他了
We crossed him off.
我知道，這是大錯特錯
I know. It's a mistake.
他年輕有為又帥氣
He's young, he's handsome. He's bright.
出了賓州就沒人知道他是誰
Nobody knows who he is  outside of Philadelphia.
沒有金主，也沒基礎建設
There's no donor base, no infrastructure.
你讓民主黨全委會給我補助
You start me offwith funding from the DNC
我會為他建立一支大軍
and I'll raise an army around this guy.
我會親自督導他的競選
I will personally oversee his campaign.
這是最佳方案嗎？
Is that the best we can do?
有什麼比一張白紙更好？
What's better than a blank slate  in the right hands?
愛德，快走吧
Ed, you need to go.
議員，你有時間嗎？
Congressman, do you have a moment?
謝謝你，派翠
Thank you, Patti.
- 叫他打電話給我  - 好
-Have him call me.  -I will.
愛德？拜託
Ed? Please.
- 什麼事？  - 我來處理
-What is going on?  -I'm taking care of it.
議員，一會兒就好，拜託
One second, sir. Please.
好吧，快點，米契
All right. Make it fast, Meechum.
我難以啟齒
It's not easy for me to ask this,
但是我在想你能不能  跟我老闆說點好話
but I was wondering if you could  put in a good word with my boss.
好話？
A good word?
他們要開除我，議員
They're going to discharge me, sir.
我很清楚我搞砸了
I messed up. I'm fully aware.
但是我的工作對我很重要
But my job, it means everything to me,
我知道你說一句好話就能…
and I know a good word from you would...
我對你個人沒有意見，米契
Look, I have nothing  against you personally, Meechum,
但是我不能干涉這類事情
but I can't get involved  in these sort of affairs.
規定就是規定
There's protocols and rules.
議員，請你和卡帝夫…
Sir, please, if you spoke to Cardiff...
我無能為力
There is nothing that I can do.
只有你能說服隊長了，議員
If anyone could convince the Captain,  it would be you, Congressman.
抱歉，祝你好運，米契
I'm sorry. I wish you all the best, Meechum.
道格
Doug.
邦尼霍爾說了什麼？
What did Barney Hull say?
我們會是第一個知道
That we'd be the first to know.
不敢相信  到現在還沒有報警電話
I can't believe there hasn't been  a single 911 call.
是有很多  但不是我們要的那種
There's been plenty.  It's just not the sort we're after.
亞特蘭大的孩子
We got that kid in Atlanta.
不行，得要是這裏的  我不能去搭飛機
No, it's got to be here.  I can't be getting on a plane.
看起來太取巧了
It looks too opportunistic.
或許該擴大範圍？
Maybe if we open it up a little bit?
我們不能降低水準
No, we cannot lower our standards.
再耐心等等
We just have to be patient.
新規則，既然辯論結束了
New rule. Now that the debate's over,
法蘭安德沃  得告訴我們究竟怎麼回事
Frank Underwood has to tell us  what the hell that was.
母音運動
說真的，議員，那是開玩笑嗎？
Seriously, Congressman, was that a joke?
我好久沒看過這種事…
I haven't seen something  just lay there like that since...
得回溯到我的高中舞會
I gotta go all the way back to my prom night.
拜託解決這場罷工
Can we just settle this strike please?
教師離開教室很久了
Teachers have been out  of the classroom for so long,
中學生開始偷嘗禁果
middle-schoolers are starting to  have sex with each other.
夠了
Enough.
我不懂你為什麼要看
I don't know why you had it on  in the first place.
我愛你，法蘭斯
I love you, Francis.
我知道
I know.
我們該多對彼此說這句話
We should say that more often to each other.
我得清理思緒
I need to clear my head.
…在機場北邊與東邊
...north and east of the airport.
開會前幫我弄好
I'm gonna need that in time for that meeting.
彼得，我們談談吧
Peter, let's talk.
我和派翠西亞惠特克談過  她同意了
So. I've spoken to Patricia Whittaker.  She's on board.
你會得到民主黨全委會  四百萬啟動補助
You'll be getting $4 million  in start-up funding from the DNC.
我來挑選團隊，你八月宣佈
I'll pick the team. You announce in August.
但是選戰今天就展開
But the campaign starts today.
你做好準備了嗎？
Are you ready?
我已經擬好一份政綱
I've already put together a platform.
還是泛泛之論  但我們可以多加琢磨
It's mostly broad strokes, but we can hone it.
很好，我們的首要任務  就是你戒酒
Good. The first thing we need to address  is your sobriety.
你不用擔心
You don't need to worry about that.
你有參加聚會嗎？
Have you been going to meetings?
你是說戒酒會？
You mean AA?
- 對  - 我不喜歡這檔子事
-Yes.  -That's not really my thing.
如果你要我幫忙
If you want my help,
那參加聚會是我的要求
then going to meetings  is my one requirement.
我知道我有酗酒問題，法蘭
I know I had a problem, Frank.
我承認
I accept that.
我對此負責
And I've taken responsibility for that,
但是沒必要去參加聚會
but I don't think going to  meetings is necessary.
你在恢復期  不能靠意志力撐下去，彼得
You cannot white-knuckle  your recovery, Peter.
這場競選會是  你一生做過最艱困的事
This campaign will be the hardest thing  you've ever done in your life.
我明白，我準備好了
I realize that. I'm prepared for that.
你認為你準備好了
You think you are.
但是我們經不起任何風險
But we can't take any chances.
黨部對你寄予厚望
The party's investing in you.
我必須確保你全力以赴
I need to make sure  you're investing in yourself.
好吧，我會盡力而為
All right. I'll do whatever I have to do.
很好，明早開始
Good. You'll start tomorrow morning.
- 道格會帶你去  - 史坦普？
-Doug will take you.  -Stamper?
他戒酒14年了
He's been sober 14 years.
道格有酗酒問題？
Doug has a drinking problem?
曾經，現在沒了  他會當你的保證人
Had. Not anymore. He'll be your sponsor.
同時，我要你  去見我的老婆，克萊兒
In the meantime, I want you  to meet with my wife, Claire.
她推動淨水創權
She runs the Clean Water lnitiative.
她等著見你
She's expecting you,
所以空出你的行程  現在就去那裏
so clear your schedule  and head over there now.
法蘭
Frank.
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝你相信我
For believing in me.
你會是絕佳候選人，彼得
You're gonna make a great candidate, Peter.
造船廠關閉空出  一千一百英畝的聯邦土地
The shipyard closing  frees up 1,100 acres of federal land.
我們的目的是  通過德拉瓦河分水嶺法案
Our goal is to pass a Watershed Act  for the Delaware River.
我們用環保方式開發土地
We develop the land in an  environmentally responsible way,
同時創造工作機會
creating jobs in the process.
- 多少工作？  - 數以千計
-How many jobs?  -Thousands.
目標收益兩億
We're aiming for the $200 million mark.
我們有一堆事要做
We got a lot of work to do.
沒錯，但你能從議員著手
We do, but you can start  with the congressmen
找出落在分水嶺內的選區
whose districts fall within the watershed.
你能給看我草案嗎？
Do you have a draft of the bill  you can show me?
我們從未發起環境立法
We haven't sponsored  any environmental legislation.
我是史提夫，別回電  煩請造訪…
我們會和你的手下  討論草案內容
We'll draft it in consultation with your staff.
吉莉安是這邊的主要負責人
Gillian will be the point person on our end.
我沒有立法經驗
I don't have any legislation experience.
- 我會幫你  - 何時開始？
-I'll help you.  -When do we start?
已經開始了
We just did.
介紹他給研究小組
Will you introduce him to the research team?
- 我等會就過去  - 好的
-I'll be there in one second.  -Sure.
明天可以嗎？
總統先生？
Mr. President?
結束這一切
I want it over.
- 越快越好  - 修改提案，法蘭
-As soon as possible.  -Gut the bill, Frank.
採取必要措施結束罷工
Do whatever's necessary to end this.
總統先生，如果現在屈服
Mr. President, if we give in now,
大眾不會覺得你贏得勝利
the public won't credit you with a victory.
連邊都沾不上  他們會說我們節節敗退
Not even a hollow one.  They'll chalk it up as a colossal defeat.
那是你的過失，法蘭
Well, that's on you, Frank.
你讓局勢演變得一發不可收拾
You let this situation devolve to where it is.
美國史上最大規模教師罷工  使我備受指摘
I've already been blamed  for the largest teachers' strike in U.S. history.
我不會為歹戲拖棚負責
I won't be held accountable  for it dragging on months and months.
總統先生  我們要用你的關係結束罷工
Mr. President, we have to  end this strike on your terms.
- 不能用別人的  - 怎麼做？
-Not anyone else's.  -How?
和馬帝史皮奈拉在CNN辯論？
By debating Marty Spinella on CNN?
總統，你一向對我信任有加
Sir, you have placed your faith in me thus far.
我懇求你繼續信任我
I would ask that you continue to do so.
你的做法毫無效用，法蘭  所以我要介入
Well, whatever you're doing, Frank,  isn't working, so I'm stepping in.
照琳達說的，修改提案
Gut the bill. Like Linda said.
不行
No.
抱歉，總統先生，我辦不到
I'm sorry, Mr. President, but I will not do that.
你讓驕傲沖昏腦袋了，法蘭？
Are you letting pride  cloud your judgment, Frank?
恕我直言，總統  是你讓恐懼沖昏你的腦袋
Respectfully, sir,  you're allowing fear to cloud yours.
對自由世界最有權勢的人
Not an easy thing, to say no
說不並不容易
to the most powerful man in the free world.
但有時唯一  能贏取上級尊重的方法
But sometimes the only way  to gain your superior's respect
就是違抗
is to defy him.
琳達，今天行程是？
What do we have on the schedule, Linda?
你要和聯邦監督委員會開會
Your meeting with the  Fed Oversight Committee.
謝謝，總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
- 你有我的簡報？  - 這裏
-Do you have my briefing?  -Right here.
很好，我們看一遍
Good. Let's look it over.
掃瞄代碼- 地圖
你好，和彼得談得如何？
Hi. How'd it go with Peter?
很順利
It went well.
- 他投入嗎？  - 非常投入
-ls he game?  -Completely.
謝謝
Thank you.
我如釋重負
That's a big weight off my shoulders.
你聽起來很疲憊
You sound tired.
疲憊、不耐煩
Tired. Impatient.
我能幫什麼忙？
What can I do?
不用了，這只能聽天由命
Nothing. This one's up to fate.
我不喜歡聽天由命
I don't like when we leave things to fate.
我也不喜歡
Neither do I.
這是說我今晚得獨守空閨？
Does that mean I'm gonna have  the bed to myself tonight?
可能吧
Probably.
道格不能頂替你嗎？
Can't Doug man the fort?
他可以，但是我會輾轉難眠
Well, he could, but I'd just toss and turn.
既然睡不著  乾脆在這裏熬夜好了
If I'm not gonna sleep,  I might as well not sleep here.
好吧，我會開著手機
Well, I'll leave the ringer on.
想要人陪伴就打電話給我
Call me if you want company.
好，晚安
I will. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
你應該回家  我可以處理剩下的
You should go home.  I could take it from here.
謹慎，這有益無害
Vigilance. It's good for the soul.
安檢，16街和Q街轉角
10-59. Corner of 16th and Q. 10-59.
那是什麼？
What's that?
妨礙治安
Disorderly conduct.
你信因果報應嗎？
Do you believe in karma?
當然不信
Absolutely not.
我信
Well, I do.
至少今晚
At least tonight.
打電話給卡帝夫隊長
Get Captain Cardiff on the phone.
我們來處理米契的事
Let's do something about Meechum.
- 什麼？  - 幫他保住飯碗
-What?  -Get him his job back.
他開槍了
He fired his weapon.
他反應過度
He overreacted.
現在就打給卡帝夫
Cardiff. On the phone. Now.
南茜，幫我接卡帝夫隊長
Nancy, give me Captain Cardiff, please.
反正也是等  不如做點有用的事
We might as well do one  productive thing while we wait.
這對我只是舉手之勞  對他卻意義重大
It requires very little of me  and will mean the world to him.
這是非常便宜的投資
It's a very inexpensive investment.
我是道格史坦普
Hello, sir. This is Doug Stamper.
法蘭斯安德沃想跟你談話
I have Francis Underwood for you.
我接通了
I got him on.
隊長，我知道很晚了
Captain, I know it's late,
但是我想和你談談  愛德華米契的事
but I'd like to talk to you  about Edward Meechum.
早安，先生
Good morning, gentlemen.
謝謝
Thank you.
餓嗎？
Are you hungry?
進來難嗎？
You have any trouble getting in?
不會，只是他們用X光  檢查了兩遍食物
No, they made me put it through  the X-ray machine twice,
希望不要過熟才好
so I hope it didn't overcook it.
法蘭，你每次都付太多錢  這樣太多了
Frank, you always pay too much.  This is way too much.
這是為了彌補你的不便
It's for the inconvenience.
你光顧我的店20年了
You know, 20 years  you been coming to my joint.
我頭一回來你辦公室
This is the first time I've been to yours.
你覺得怎樣？
What do you think?
- 還不錯  - 歡迎隨時光臨
-I could get used to it.  -Well, you're welcome any time.
- 謝謝，弗萊迪  - 別客氣，法蘭
-Thank you, Freddy.  -Always, Frank.
第三街446號有起…
We got a 27 Delta two. 446 3rd Street...
- 那是駕車槍擊  - 查出細節
-That's a drive-by shooting.  -Get details.
議員，謝謝你和隊長說情
Sir, I want to thank you  for talking to the Captain.
他告訴我你打了電話  真是感激不盡
He told me you called,  and I can't tell you how grateful I am.
我要你仔細聽清楚
I want you to listen very closely
我現在說的話
to what I'm about to say.
從現在起，你就是石頭
From this moment on, you are a rock.
不聽信他人之言，守口如瓶
You absorb nothing, you say nothing,
如金剛不摧
and nothing breaks you.
- 明白嗎？  - 是的，議員
-ls that clear?  -Yes, sir.
歡迎歸隊
Welcome back.
史提夫？
Steve?
我就不打擾你們了
I'll leave you be.
珍妮…在哪？
Where... Where's Janet?
過去這幾周她每天守在這兒
She's been here every day  for the last few weeks.
我要她回家休息
I told her, go home, get some rest.
一切都好嗎？
Well, is everything okay?
你傳簡訊說很重要
Your text said it was important.
我不知該如何啟齒
I don't know how to put this.
事情是這樣的，我…
The thing is, l...
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
許多事
A lot.
想我這輩子
About my life.
想我沒做過的事
About the things I haven't done.
我沒說過的話
Things I haven't said.
我恨你的老公
I hate your husband.
許多人恨他
A lot of people do.
過去八年來，我看守著他
The past eight years, I watched over him.
但我看的不是他
But it wasn't him I was watching.
每回我見到你
And every time I saw you,
每次我聽到你的聲音
every time I heard your voice,
我能想到的就是
all I could think to myself was,
「天啊，我願付出一切」
"Jesus, what I wouldn't give."
這個念頭在我心中盤旋無數回
I can't tell you how many times  I thought about that.
你知道法蘭斯向我求婚時  說什麼嗎？
You know what Francis said to me  when he proposed?
我記得他的一字一句
I remember his exact words.
他說：  「克萊兒  如果你只求快樂
He said, "Claire, if all you want is happiness,
「那就拒絕吧
"say no.
「我不會跟你生好幾個孩子
"I'm not gonna give you a couple of kids
「倒數退休的日子
"and count the days until retirement.
「我保證你不會這樣
"l promise you freedom from that.
「我保證你永遠不會感到無聊」
"l promise you'll never be bored."
他是唯一一個
You know, he was the only man,
以前我有許多追求者
and there were a lot of others who proposed.
但他是唯一懂我的人
But he was the only one who understood me.
他不把我當女神看待
He didn't put me on some pedestal.
他知道我不想被崇拜或寵愛
He knew that I didn't want to be  adored or coddled.
所以他拿起我的手  為我戴上戒指
So he took my hand and he put a ring on it.
因為他知道我會答應
Because he knew I'd say yes.
他知道怎麼  取得自己想要的事物
He's a man who knows  how to take what he wants.
這是你要的嗎？
Is this what you wanted?
你想要這樣嗎？
Is that the way you wanted it?
住手
Stop. Stop.
拜託，住手
Please. Please. Stop.
不要
Don't.
你告訴我實話
You told me your truth.
現在你也知道我的了
Now you know mine.
彼得魯索
我是彼得
Hey, it's Peter.
我不期待你回電
I don't expect you to call me back,
但是我想讓你知道  我昨晚停止喝酒了
but I wanted to let you know  I stopped drinking last night,
今早第一次去戒酒聚會
and I went to my first  AA meeting this morning.
我該彌補那些受我傷害的人
I'm supposed to reach out  and make amends to those I've hurt.
但是我想打電話給你
But I guess the real reason I called you
其實是想說我愛你，我想你
is just to say I love you and I miss you.
我希望你一切都好
I hope you're well.
這是工作，不是玩樂
This is work, not play.
那你為什麼過來？
Then why'd you bother coming over?
我本來希望你光溜溜來開門
I was hoping you'd answer the door naked.
那會是玩樂
That would be play.
那會是有看頭的工作
That would be work with a view.
抱歉讓你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
一則推文能寫幾個字？
How many characters in a tweet?
140個字
140.
寫下我的話  告訴我寫了幾個字
Type this, let me know where you land.
八歲的華府男孩
Eight-year-old Washington D.C. boy
在幫派槍戰中遭流彈射中死亡
killed by a stray bullet  in gangland shoot-out.
還剩61個字
61 characters left.
他應該在學校？
He should have been in school?
還剩30個字
30 left.
史皮奈拉的責任，問號
Spinella to blame. Question mark.
- 128個字  - 按傳送
-128.  -Press send.
給我名字、細節
Now give me a name, details.
泰勒戴維  就讀維蒙貝克小學三年級
Tyler Davis. Third-grader  at Vernon Baker Elementary.
今天接近中午時  在東南區的家門外中槍
Shot outside his home in Southeast  just before noon today.
傳送了，你要去哪？
Sent. Where are you going?
- 去探望死者母親  - 你不想…
-To see the mother.  -You don't wanna...
有事要辦，晚點來看你
There's work to do. I'll see you later tonight.
泰勒從沒做過壞事
Tyler never did anything wrong.
他是個好孩子
He was a good boy.
大家都愛他
Everybody loved him.
沒事了
It's okay.
如果泰勒的學校有上課
If Tyler's school had been in session,
就不會被錯殺了
this senseless killing  would have never taken place.
我們必須立刻結束罷工
We need to end this strike now
讓所有孩子回到學校
and get all our children  back in school where they belong,
以免發生類似的死亡事件
before we risk another death like this.
史皮奈拉先生  我現在就去國會大樓
So, Mr. Spinella, I am headed  to the Capitol right now,
等你來和我談話
and I will remain there until  you are ready to meet and talk
讓我們結束這場沒意義的罷工
so that we can end this pointless strike.
謝謝大家前來
Thank you all for coming.
我們進去吧
Let's go back inside.
史皮奈拉先生，就一個問題
Mr. Spinella, one question.
史皮奈拉先生目前無可奉告
Mr. Spinella is not gonna  make comments at this time.
無可奉告
No comment. No comment.
謝謝
Thank you.
法蘭
Frank.
怎樣？
So?
你說你想談談
You said you wanted to talk.
你說你想找出妥協方案
You said you wanted to  work out a compromise.
我說謊
I lied.
什麼？
Excuse me?
我無意找出妥協方案
I have no intention  of working out a compromise.
那在這裏會面是要怎樣，法蘭？
So then why the fuck are we here, Frank?
你有什麼毛病？  你以為這是什麼遊戲嗎？
What the hell's the matter with you?  You think this is some kind of a game?
不是
No.
這些人有家庭要養
These are real people with families to feed.
你可以停止嗎？
Would you please stop that?
停止什麼？
Stop what?
再五秒，我就走人
In five seconds, I'm out of here.
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three.
- 四  - 再見，法蘭
-Four.  -Goodbye, Frank.
馬帝，你知道你我的差別嗎？
You know the difference  between you and me, Marty?
什麼？
What?
我是來自貧窮白人小鎮的窮白人
I'm a white-trash cracker  from a white-trash town
根本無人理會
that no one would even bother to piss on.
但差別就在這裏
But here's the difference.
我讓自己功成名就
I've made something of myself.
我成為國會重量級人物  大家尊重我
I have the keys to the Capitol.  People respect me.
但是你呢，你什麼都不是
But you, you're still nothing.
你只是穿著昂貴西裝  盛氣凌人的義大利佬
You're just an uppity dago  in an expensive suit
向工會求歡
turning tricks for the unions.
沒人尊重工會了，馬帝
Nobody respects the unions anymore, Marty.
工會就快滅亡，沒人尊重你
They're dying. And no one respects you.
你這輩子頂多就是
The most you'll ever make of yourself
為我這種人吹簫
is blowing men like me.
有真正權力的人
Men with real power.
我從這裏就聞得到  你嘴裏的騷氣
Yes. I can smell the cock  on your breath from here.
你以為這樣能讓我發火？
You think you can get under my skin?
- 我知道我可以  - 是
-I know I can.  -Yeah.
去死吧，法蘭
Kiss my ass, Frank.
- 你不敢走出去的  - 走著瞧
-You can't afford to walk out.  -Watch me.
我這裏有個死去的貧困孩子
I've got a dead,  underprivileged kid in my pocket.
你有什麼？
What do you have?
兩百萬受敬重的教師
I have two million honorable teachers.
說得好，但我還有更棒的
Fair enough. But I got something even better.
來吧，打開
Go ahead. Open it.
好吧
Okay.
我就陪你玩這場遊戲
I'll play your game.
你是白癡
You're an idiot.
是史坦普丟的
Stamper threw it.
你胡扯
You're full of shit.
磚頭是史坦普丟的
No, Stamper threw the brick.
我要克萊兒支開保全
And I made sure Claire  distracted my security.
你在開玩笑嗎？
Are you kidding me?
你還要我向我老婆道歉
And to think you wanted me  to apologize to my wife.
你居然做如此下流的事，法蘭？
You would do something that low, Frank?
我設下磚頭的局，馬帝
I arranged the brick, Marty,
正如我安排今天下午這場會面
just like I arranged  this meeting this afternoon.
後退，法蘭
Back off, Frank.
你何不跪下
Why don't you just get down on your knees
- 回到你的位置？  - 後退，法蘭
-where you really belong?  -Back off, Frank.
你唯一能從我身上得到的
Because the only thing  you're gonna get from me
- 就是射精…  - 去你的！
-is cum on your...  -Fuck you!
議員，一切還好嗎？
Everything okay in there, sir?
我會說是你挑釁我
Look, I'll tell them you provoked me.
我會說是你自己丟磚塊
I'll tell them that you threw the brick yourself.
誰會相信你呢？
And who's going to believe you?
你剛襲擊美國議員
You just assaulted  a United States Congressman,
這是重罪
which is a felony.
但是我不會起訴，馬帝
But I'm not gonna press charges, Marty.
因為罷工就此結束
Because the strike ends now.
會留下疤痕嗎？
You think it'll leave a scar?
我的皮很厚
I have a thick skin.
下次你要我邀人進來喝咖啡
The next time you ask me  to invite someone in for coffee,
拜託別弄到擦槍走火
will you please make sure no guns go off?
我會盡力
I'll do my best.
我今天又去看了史提夫
I saw Steve again today.
- 他還好嗎？  - 很痛苦
-How is he?  -ln a lot of pain.
我該去看他嗎？
Should I go see him?
不用了
I don't think you need to.
喬伊邦斯
Zoe Barnes.
他過世後，我們幫他出錢辦喪禮
When he dies, we'll pay for his funeral.
你不接嗎？
You don't need to take it?
不了
No.
我今天忙完工作了
I'm done with work today.